You've lived long enough.
You'll pay with your life
for what you did to me.
Father!
This is the end, Osman.
I'll wipe you off with
your state from the history.
Neither this arrow nor
any of you can defeat me.
-You'll kneel before me, Osman.
-I won't kneel before you.
-I'll only make you kneel.
-Attack!
Where are you going, red devil?
I wish I could stay, Bala.
But I have to live to give
you the worst suffering.
Soldiers, kill!
Wait, Poena. Not now.
Don't take this off.
Poena
Osman, Sofia is running away!
I shot Osman.
Why are we running away,
aunt? We can kill him now.
Poena, there are too many
soldiers. I can't risk you.
-Aunt, no!
-Poena.
We'll take revenge during
their most unprotected moment.
They'll definitely find the tunnel.
-We should kill them here.
-Don't worry.
If they follow us, that
will be a disaster for them.
Let's go. Let's go!
Bala, there must be a tunnel.
They couldn't go out
otherwise. Orhan, you got this.
-Alright, my Bey.
-Let's go.
Allah is the greatest!
Come on.
You went through this, huh?
She left with someone but I couldn't see.
They can't go anywhere.
We'll trap them.
Why did we stop, aunt?
Someone's following us.
But they don't know this is my place.
Come on, Poena! The tunnel is going to collapse.
The demon ran fast.
She's disappeared.
We'll find him even if
they go deep into hell!
-Why stop? They're running off.
-Stop. I smell something.
Run!
Alaaddin, come on
-I'm coming, brother!
-Brother, let's go!
Karesiogullari Beylic
I will make life unbearable for you.
I swear.
I will make you face fall on the ground!
-You'll see. Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
How did Osman get rid of you?
My Bey, we didn't attack to
avoid harming Begum Hatun.
We thought Osman Bey would kill her, but...
..thanks to Allah he didn't.
Well...
Did Begum Hatun get rid of Osman herself?
She managed to wriggle out of his sword, my Bey.
To be honest, she showed great courage.
Courage, huh?
Great courage...
It's great courage to
wriggle out of Osman's sword.
Beys are waiting in the council, my Bey.
Attention!
Karesi Bey!
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you, too.
Here is my order.
My army will be ready
fully-equipped for the war.
As you order my Bey!
Words are over now.
Blood has been shed.
From now on, only swords will speak.
We're starting a great war.
Before Osman kneels before
me and kisses my flag,
..this war won't end!
God willing, my Bey!
Only I can start and end wars in these lands.
For this reason, I'm the one to decide in
which battlefield the fight will take place!
My army will be ready
fully-equipped in Yassiova.
As you order my Bey!
-Are you alright?
-I'm good.
-I'm good, Bala. You?
-I'm fine.
-My Bey!
-Mother, are you alright?
Are you alright?
-We're fine.
We're good. Don't worry.
This place is going to collapse. Out!
Come on, come on
They laid a trap there in advance, my Bey.
The dog called Sofia...
Her mind works like the devil's.
She always has another plan.
My Bey.
Your bleeding is going worse.
-I should cauterize the wound.
-No.
This wound can't harm my Bey.
It's just a badge in his chest.
I'm good. Don't worry.
We killed all the heathens
in the temple, my Bey.
But the dastard called Lukas ran away.
Hearing the explosion, we rushed here.
He is living his last moments.
I'll cut off his head soon.
We're going to the tribe.
Until both Sofia and Lukas lose their heads
...we won't even sleep! Let's go.
Karesi Bey sped up his war preparations.
But I found out the location
of their headquarters.
Deliver this to Osman Bey
without being seen by anyone.
As you order, my lady.
Karesi Bey was right to be suspicious.
You are Osman Bey's spy, huh?
Let my spilled blood be a witness.
Osman and his children all of them...
..all of them Sofia..
I will not die until all of them are dead.
I swear to you I will not die.
This is the last wound
Osman inflicted on us, Lukas.
It will not happen again.
I was so close.
I was going to kill Osman and Bala.
Why, aunt?
Why?
Poena.
My little bird.
What did I say?
For you, for your life.
-They didn't see your face, right?
-They didn't.
I shot Osman aunt.
If I could shoot one more
arrow, he would have died.
Come here.
You will do it.
You will get much closer to them and kill them.
The time has come.
Our game begins.
Welcome our Bey! Welcome!
My Bey.
Osman Bey, you are wounded.
Does your wound hurt much?
I'm alright, don't worry.
Ayse, why are you asking if his
wound hurts in front of people?
He is the leader of a state!
Even if it hurts, he doesn't let them see it!
How do you know this?
I know, Osman Bey, I know.
Today, the decision of a leader
won, not the schemes of infidels!
Look at you, who teaches you this? Cerkutay?
Those who spend time with
wolves learn how to howl my Bey.
My Bey.
Is there any news from the...
..Sofia or Lukas infidels?
We destroyed Sofia's nest and her soldiers.
For now, she escaped.
But Sofia and Lukas will
be erased from these lands.
And Karesi Bey, her collaborator, will
also pay for what he did. Don't worry!
God willing.
Come on.
-Let's start the council.
-As you order, my Bey.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come in.
You were right to be suspicious, my Bey.
Begum Hatun sent a letter to
Osman Bey through her helper.
So, you have been betraying
us all along, Begum Hatun?
If I am Karesi Bey, I will
not let you get away with this.
Shall we kill Begum Hatun's helper
before she takes the letter to him, my Bey?
No.
We will not harm either
the helper or Begum Hatun.
They will think I don't know.
Through Begum, I will set
such a trap for Osman that...
How did you do this to her?
I told you not to
underestimate me, Lukas.
Yes...
But how?
When you kidnapped her, she was old
enough to remember her family, wasn't she?
She was a child.
Children love fairy tales the most.
Fairy tales are full of lies.
Master Yannis's student Martin prepared
a potion to make her forget everything.
Father, where are you?
Poena.
Are you awake?
My name is Halime.
Your name is Poena.
Are you hungry?
I brought you milk.
Poena..
Look, if you drink this...
...your father will come.
Will you drink this?
Well done, my daughter.
Good girl.
Well done.
Almost done.
Soon, you won't remember a thing.
Your pain will go away.
Well done.
My little bird.
Are you sure?
Are you sure she forgot
everything? What if she remembers?
That will never happen, Lukas!
Poena is tied to me not by blood...
...but by something stronger.
-Love.
-Love?
You and love?
Me and love.
Then what will you do, Sofia?
What will you do when everything is over?
Won't you kill her?
Osman took my future, Lukas.
He destroyed Master Yannis'
lineage. But with Poena...
..I will continue Master Yannis' teachings.
The swords are drawn.
We are at war with Karesi.
This will be a battlefield war
But Karesi cannot be trusted.
For his interests, he might
attack us from other places.
That's why we will be more cautious...
...in all our cities, tribes, and castles...
...where our flag flies...
...together with our people and soldiers.
Prepare everything.
-As you order, my Bey.
-As you order my Bey.
-As you order my Bey. -After the sun rises...
...we will fight against Karesi.
-Yes my Bey.
If he faces us, that will be good.
If not...
...we will attack each of his properties.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Yagiz.
My Bey, Yusuf Bey.
He is asking for your
permission to come in, my Bey.
Let him in.
My Bey, there is news
from my sister Begum Hatun.
-She sent her helper to the tribe.
-What did she say?
At the council, Karesi Bey said,
"If Osman Bey wants a battlefield...
...I will decide which
field it will take place."
He has placed his quarters near Yassova, my Bey.
Is that so?
So he accepts the battlefield.
Bayhan Bey...
Tomorrow, you will place
our quarters near Yassova.
Until the army arrives, the
headquarter's safety is in your hands.
I will do everything I can, Osman Bey.
As you say.
Tomorrow..
...the fate of these lands will be decided.
This war..
This will be a war between those
who walk with The Righteous' guidance...
...and those who stray from the right path.
Finally, you have found
the right path, Begum Hatun.
Thanks to those who showed me the right way.
You know..
Begum Hatun not only entered my council...
-She will soon become my wife.
-I know.
I know, Karesi Bey. Good.
Then let me give you my wedding gift.
In the war you will fight, I will
be behind you with all my power.
My power is enough to destroy Osman.
But I will also give you the
opportunity to take revenge.
I am eager to hear your war plans, Karesi Bey.
Come, Lukas.
I have set up such a
plan that I will attack
Osman before he even
arrives on the battlefield.
How?
Osman will set up his headquarters near Yassova.
I will attack him with catapults from a hill.
I will destroy his Alps and supplies
before they even reach the battlefield.
So, on the day of the war,
Osman will be weak and helpless.
That's smart.
Osman will pay the price
for competing with you...
...Karesi Bey.
Begum Hatun.
You seem tired.
You can rest a bit if you like.
I haven't slept well in the past few nights.
I think I better rest. Excuse me.
Sure.
Go, you spy.
Go and deliver the news to Osman.
What are you saying, Karesi Bey?
Is Begum Hatun a traitor?
Then this is all a game.
There will be no attack.
There will be.
But it's you who'll perform.
Osman will think I will attack.
But I will only waste his time.
The one attacking the headquarters...
..will be you, Lukas.
Do you like wearing those ugly clothes?
No.
Just..
I just feel like I'm someone
else in these clothes, aunt.
To make sure you don't forget yourself.
My little bird.
It belonged to your mother...
Nevadoka.
My little...
...my little revenge angel.
The big day has come.
Tomorrow, you will convince
Fatma and enter the Kayi Tribe.
And you will kill your mother's murderer, Bala.
I will kill her.
But...
...what if Osman doesn't die in the war?
What if he returns to the tribe?
Osman.
If Osman returns to the
tribe and sees Bala dead...
...half of his life will be gone anyway.
And you will take..
..the other half.
So, they love each other
enough to die for one another.
You will destroy that family.
As they destroyed your family.
You will take your mother's
and father's revenge.
Bala, were you able to see the face of
the person Sofia took with her? Who was it?
No my Bey.
We don't know who is important for Sofia.
So there is someone she cares.
You are talking about Sofia. She is the devil.
There's no goodwill or compassion in her.
Whoever she took must
definitely be someone useful to her.
When we cornered her, I tried to
make her talk, but she didn't say anything.
Even that might be a game, huh?
-She must have something evil in her mind.
-You're right.
Now they will unite with Karesi.
Yes, they will...
But Karesi Bey..
We had to get into this war because of him.
So much blood will be shed because of his greed.
If they unite, they will
become too strong, Osman.
How will we get out of that circle of fire?
No matter how strong they become...
...we will destroy that evil alliance.
Let's pray that..
...Begum Hatun does not get exposed.
The days have come when
we even pray for Begum Hatun.
Let her fulfill her duty
properly, that's all we need.
Are the weapons ready? What's the situation?
Smiths are working, my Bey.
Good.
All the preparations should be finished by
the time our army reaches the headquarters.
As you order, my Bey.
What's the matter? Just spill the beans.
Nothing, my Bey.
I'm thinking about the times when
I dreamed of fighting beside you.
My childhood...
Whenever we fight together
now, that child feels happy, father.
May Allah be pleased with you.
-My brave son.
Thank Allah for letting us see these days.
I know that the tribe
won't stay without a head...
...if my life ends today.
What do you mean, father?
May Allah give you a long life.
Well... I know my brave
son will protect my heritage.
That's why no battles can intimidate Bayhan Bey.
Attention! Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you, too, my Bey.
Bayhan Bey, what is the situation?
All the preparations done in the headquarter?
Defense pits, patrols and food silos...
We took all the measures as you ordered, my Bey.
Did you increase the numbers of
the scouts around the tribe, Gonca?
Everybody is on alert as you warned, mother.
Good. Ulgen!
You checked the food to
go to the headquarter, right?
I prepared more than enough, Bala. Don't worry.
Good, good. Alps!
Be cautious.
Take it to the headquarter in no time.
As you order, Bala Hatun.
Come on, come on.
While our army is preparing for the war,
...we will continue trading.
So we will keep inspecting the stalls, hatuns.
We have much to do.
Hatuns.
Is there a problem?
Just name it. And we will solve it.
Isn't Gonca Hatun here?
Gonca Hatun..
...is on another duty.
I'm here now.
Holofira Hatun, wife of Orhan Bey!
I'm in charge here as a Kayi hatun.
And this is the last time I say this.
While our soldiers and
alps risk their lives for us
...you will perform your duties...
...instead of asking impertinent questions!
Otherwise I will forgive no mistakes!
Now..
Get back to your work!
Praise be to my sister-in-law.
All of them will come around...
...and accept you.
I won't let any other ways, Fatma.
Meryem, are you alright? What's wrong?
My grandmother... She has died, Fatma Hatun.
I have nobody else.
I don't know what to do.
I'm so sorry.
My condolences.
But don't be too hard on yourself.
Allah gives lives and takes lives.
I have no money and no food.
I have nowhere to go.
I know...
You train Sisters.
Won't you let me join?
-Can you use a sword?
-I can if you teach me.
Even if I can't, I can cook for Sisters.
And wash their clothes.
Please don't leave me alone, Fatma Hatun.
Nobody will be alone in
Osman Bey's land, Meryem.
May Allah be pleased with you, Fatma Hatun.
Come on, let me introduce you to Sisters.
Karesiogullari Beylic
You wanted to see me, Karesi Bey?
Where are we going?
We're going to watch Osman's
quarters be destroyed, Begum Hatun.
What?
Are you unhappy for this?
Just the opposite.
My biggest dream is to see
Osman's being defeated, Karesi Bey.
Let's not be late then.
-Kanyumaz, alps?
-They're waiting for us on the hill, my Bey.
Come on then.
We should go.
Victory is waiting for us.
Tell experienced watchmen...
...not only to watch around our quarters...
...but also watch beyond
Karesi Bey's headquarters.
We should know whatever moves.
As you order, my Bey.
Aykurt Cavus.
My Bey.
We got a message from Begum Hatun.
Dastard.
What's written, my Bey?
Karesi and Byzantine made
a plan against us together.
Over there... Near Yassiova.
He's going to hit the quarters with catapults.
-Vile dog!
-He is!
He's too scared to face us on the battlefield.
We'll go there before catapults start shooting
Bring the horses!
Bayhan Bey, you have the command here.
-Keep your eyes wide open.
-As you order, my Bey.
Let's go.
Come on, alps!
Keep training
Karesi Bey did his part and got
Osman out of his headquarters.
Get ready.
Osman thinks the attack
will come from catapults.
But hell will spread in his
headquarters with our swords!
Commander Lukas, the convoy that
left Osman's tribe are approaching.
It's your turn, Sofia.
Come on, Sofia.
Kill them all!
Wear their alps' clothes!
We're going to burn down their headquarters!
-Are the catapults ready, Kanyumaz?
-Yes, my Bey.
They're behind that hill.
They're waiting for your call.
Begum Hatun.
I think... After we destroy
Osman's headquarters,
...we should go back and get married just today.
In such a time? What's the haste, my Bey?
There are enemies..
There are spies and traitors...
There are many people who want
to stab me in the back, Begum Hatun.
What do you mean, Karesi Bey?
There may be no coming back.
We should get married.
So all my properties will
be yours if I die in the war.
May Allah give you a long life, my Bey.
I have no desire for properties.
There's revenge I need
to take. I only want that.
Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
Where are the catapults?
Behind that hill, my Bey.
You look so excited, Meryem.
You did me such a favor, Fatma Hatun
...that I thought I was left
alone in the morning, but...
...I reached my biggest dream thanks to you.
Come on.
Let's make you settle in your tent first.
Then we will join the training.
Will Bala Hatun let me join Sisters?
Mother Bala won't appreciate easily.
But she will accept you.
Let's go.
Mother.
The healing house's needs got
loaded in the cart. It's ready to leave.
Good. When the other cart is
ready, make them leave immediately.
As you order, mother.
Bala Hatun.
Kismet.
Isn't Fatma here yet?
She is.
-She's brought a guest.
-A guest?
Let's see who it is.
Come on.
There are no watchers or catapults...
...on the hill or behind it.
If the information we got is true, it
seems they haven't taken action yet.
Even so,
there have to be a few watchmen at least.
There is something else going on.
What else, Osman?
Karesi.
Only Karesi? What about Bey?
I don't care what others call you.
You are only Karesi to me.
So be it, Osman.
So be it.
Tell me. What are you looking for here?
Are you here to see how more
powerful my army is than yours?
We're going to destroy his quarters today.
Look, Osman.
Look down carefully.
Look carefully.
We're in the field of truth.
Field of truth, huh?
What is the truth?
The truth is..
...that only one of us will survive here.
And no matter what sins we committed,
...the history will justify
the survivor in this field.
Yes, of course.
You're ready to commit any sins...
...to get your name written...
...among the best warriors and sultans.
You wouldn't avoid working with
heathens against your own kin, right?
-Ha?
-I wouldn't, Osman.
When I become the only ruler of the frontiers,
I will take care of those heathens too.
And then I will be ready to pay for my sins.
Now tell me... You were looking for
catapults ready to shoot your quarters.
Did you find them?
Disgrace of Turks!
Sister!
My wife-to-be.
Did you think your betrayal
wouldn't be revealed?
You're the one who betrays!
Don't, Osman.
If you take one step closer,
..your spy will die.
Sister!
You say..
...you aren't going to hit
my quarters with catapults.
Then tell me.
What game are you up to?
Be patient, Osman.
You will find out.
I didn't draw you here in vain.
You will see it for sure.
Get ready.
Soon this place will turn into a bloodbath.
Move the stakes.
Kill the Alps. -Alps!
Sofia
Alps, take your positions.
Go.
Flying flames.
I will not allow this.
The headquarters...
It should have exploded inside.
Come on. Come on.
I told you, those who show hostility and
disrespect to me will meet a terrible end.
Now you paid the price of
your carelessness at your headquarters...
...before this
battlefield where you faced me.
It is forbidden for you to die
fighting in a battlefield, Karesi.
I said don't, Osman.
If you want Begum Hatun
to live, look down there now.
Never forget the smoke you see.
When I have your body
under my feet on the battlefield...
...you will remember how I left you helpless.
These are your last games...
And this will be your last treachery.
Draw your sword.
Stand before me!
-Let Begum Hatun go.
-No.
Enough losses for you today.
Save your strength for tomorrow.
Just as you did in my castle..
...I will leave this place
under Begum Hatun's shadow.
Lukas will destroy your headquarters.
Kanyumaz. -My Bey. -Take her.
Sister, do not worry, we will save you.
Nothing will happen to
me, brother, do not worry.
Run Osman, run!
Many lives are lost in your headquarters.
Ilbay, Yusuf! -My Bey! -My Bey!
Go after Karesi now.
You will take Begum Hatun and
bring her back safe and sound.
Yes my Bey. -Yes my Bey. -Alps!
We are going to the
headquarters now! Immediately!
Burn and destroy everything! Hurry!
So you want to be a hero, Bayhan, huh?
But today you will taste death.
You dastard dog!
We do not attack enemies from behind like you.
Draw your sword.
You will pay for betrayal
with your life. Bayhan.
We do not fear paying the price, Lukas.
Dogs keep breeding, wolves
walk on the path they believe.
Sofia.
Why are you letting him speak? Kill him already.
Thanks to Allah..
...I am not dying in my
bed but on the battlefield.
Make your move, murderers!
They do not write "a hero" on
the grave of a dead man, Bayhan.
You..
...will die for nothing.
We fight to spread the
glorification of the Word of Allah.
You might shed our blood, but
our revenge will be taken for sure.
Then..
..where is..
..Osman?
Who will save you from our hands?
Look.
Look around you!
We set out on this journey with our shrouds.
Allah is sufficient for us.
He is the best protector.
Now drown in your own blood, Bayhan.
You will say your last words to Osman.
Sofia.
Finally, I entered into the heart of the enemy.
Bala.
My Halime!
Stop!
Let me see your face once, my daughter.
Mother!
Halime! Halime!
My daughter!
My child! Look everywhere! Look everywhere!
My daughter...
I have not seen you all this time.
Who are you?
Mother!
I was looking for you.
So you met.
We just met.
Welcome, my daughter.
Thank you.
I got excited when I saw you. Please forgive me.
It's okay, daughter...
Mother..
I told you about Meryem.
Her grandmother passed away.
She wants to join the Sisters.
Sure.
You will be trained and become a Sister.
My Fatma will take care of you.
Is there no one else besides your grandmother?
Years ago, the infidels raided our tribe.
They killed my mother and father.
I want to join the Sisters...
...and take their revenge, Bala Hatun.
I am sorry for your loss, my Meryem daughter.
I am sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Now, I should go to my tent if you allow me.
Why are you crying?
Why do you tear up when you see that
woman and make yourself look weak?
I will kill you Bala.
I swear, I will kill you.
She is a good girl.
I couldn't resist when I saw her like that.
My heart was broken into pieces.
I said "No one is left alone
in Osman Bey's lands".
Ah, my merciful daughter.
You have thought very well.
Alaeddin! -My Bey..
-Come, my son.
Look, is he alive?
He is a martyr, father.
Check everyone!
Take anyone who is still alive!
Come on! Help!
They are all martyrs.
All of them.
No.
No, don't do this, father.
Don't do this, father! No! Don't, father!
Father! Father!
Father, hang on, father!
Bayhan Bey...
Father... Father, stay with me.
Bayhan Bey!
Father... father..
Father, open your eyes!
-Bayhan Bey...
What happened? Alaeddin!
-Stay...
Alaeddin Bey will treat you.
Alaeddin, come.
He will recover, right, Alaeddin Bey?
You came just in time, my son.
Don't say that, father. Don't say that.
Alaeddin Bey.
You will heal my father, right?
Don't leave me father.
Son..
Father... Father! -My son..
Father!
Don't leave me father!
Don't leave me..
Don't leave me father..
Alaeddin Bey will heal you, father.. He will.
You will heal my father, right?
-Son...
Stop..
Stop...
Your father is telling you something.
I am pleased with you, my son.
May Allah be pleased with you as well.
My Bey... My Bey...
Tell me. Tell me.
I devoted my blood and life to your path.
Now... I am walking...
..to shahada on that way.
I just...
..want you to..
...take good...
..care of my..
..son Saruca.
Don't worry.
Your son is my son. Don't worry.
My Bey... My Bey, stay...
My Bey...
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad
is His servant and Messenger.
Father!
Indeed we belong to Allah,
and indeed to Him we will return.
I swear..
I swear, my Bey...
I swear I will take our revenge
from those who did this to you!
We will, sure we will.
Osman's headquarters is destroyed.
Thanks to Begum Hatun.
This is just the beginning, Lukas.
My Beys do not know we are allies.
When you come to the battlefield
to help, I will act as if I don't know.
You understand, right?
I do, Karesi Bey.
Let's not scare your Beys.
I swear... I swear..
You will pay for this!
Begum.
I killed your enemy, Bayhan...
But you are disrespecting me!
-Sofia...
Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
Take this traitor the castle
and put her in the dungeon.
I will punish her myself.
We will save my sister
on the way Ilbay. Let's go.
Yusuf, they are very crowded.
We might put Begum Hatun's life at risk.
What will we do then, Ilbay?
-We will abduct Begum Hatun from the castle.
-How will we do that?
By using you, Yusuf.
Come on.
Osman Bey Quarters
The way Karesi attacked us...
Even if we kill all of them...
This is a wound that will not heal easily.
How are ghazis doing?
Some of them have serious wound, my Bey.
We're doing our best to heal them.
What about the places
that got hit in the quarters?
The biggest damage happened in the
entrance of the headquarter, my Bey.
Alps are working with great
effort to reinforce the wall.
Cerkutay, Boran.
What about alps?
Since our alps became martyrs in the vile ambush
...everybody has been grieved, my Bey.
Especially Saruca Bey.
May Allah give him strength and endurance.
Aameen. Aameen.
To make them pay for the
vile actions they did to us,
..he has to stand up.
Karesi...
...will obviously collaborate with the heathens.
But we won't let them.
Orhan.
-Boran, Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Keep your eyes on Lukas.
In which castle is he keeping his army?
Find out.
Surround him in such a way..
...that they won't be able to even take
a peek from the walls to join the battle.
As you order, my Bey.
-Alaaddin.
-My Bey.
During the war between us and Karesi
...you and Gonca will have a different mission.
As you order, my Bey.
Where is Fatma?
She found a Sister, you
know. She sticks with her.
She got a companion, huh?
Good.
Nobody had got close to her after Halime.
-Mother.
-Yes?
I don't want to itch your wound.
But..
I always wanted to ask Alaaddin, but I couldn't.
How did Halime die?
Actually
..I want to know that too.
Let me tell you.
It's been ten years.
We were having hard times.
Osman Bey was at war.
When Cerkutay Bey was taken captive,
...each of us was fighting on another front.
I went to welcome a tribe.
Getting news about an attack,
..I left her there.
Halime fell down into the stream.
Because of me.
I couldn't protect her.
It wasn't your fault, Ulgen.
It's fate.
We looked for her, but...
Ten days...
They found her ten days later.
Halime!
My baby!
It's all because of me.
I'm here, my baby. Where
are you? Halime! My daughter!
Bala Hatun.
It's been ten days! Get out
of water. You're going to die!
Look carefully!
My girl?
It's easy to kill you, Bala.
I killed you while you were alive, though.
Your daughter is mine now.
I will turn her against you.
She will be your biggest enemy.
My baby!
We left the corpse in the stream.
She has Halime's clothes on her.
Her face is burned, though.
-Neither of her parents can recognize her.
-They'll find her soon.
Halime!
Your mother is here!
Come on, Bala.
Come on.
Halime!
Bala Hatun, Bala Hatun.
My girl...
Halime.
Halime!
Halime?
Halime..
Bala Hatun, don't look.
My girl... Is this you?
Bala Hatun, don't turn her around. Don't look.
Halime!
Halime, is this you?
It's alright. It's alright, my dear.
It's alright, my dear.
Your mother is here.
You'll get warm now, my baby.
We got attacked and defeated. We lost too many.
Cerkutay Bey is missing.
Ulgen..
-Sit down.
Oh Cerkutay...
What happened afterwards?
While Halime was missing
..Bala never slept.
For ten days.
Then she slept.
We got afraid that she wouldn't wake up again.
-Let me take some fresh air.
-Ulgen. Ulgen.
Is your patience made of steel?
You should have taken my life.
You lost your husband and I lost my child.
But you were always there for me.
You healed my wounds.
You are my sister, Ulgen.
Lullaby, my dear baby
Sleep well in your dream
Quietly and stilly
Mother. Mother, is that you?
Mother.
Mother, don't go.
Mother. Mother..
Why don't you show your face to me, mother?
Will you come to my dreams...
...when I kill them as my aunt says?
I promise you.
To be able to see you
..I will kill them.
Karesiogullari Beylic
When I get out of here, I will drain your
source of arrogance increasing your appetite...
...and prevent your vile intentions, Karesi Bey.
Dastards!
I want no food or water
from you! Get out of my sight!
You don't want it? Your choice.
You'll eat insects due to
starvation and come around.
You think I'm afraid of hunger?
I'd rather die than eat one
piece of food from traitors like you
Move, move!
Where are you bringing this traitor from?
Coward
Untie my hands and I will
show you who the traitor is!
Wait, traitor's brother. Just be patient.
Not your hands but your
tongue will be untied first.
He was watching the castle walls in the south.
He was hiding like a bear watching the beehive.
I was going to kill him, but
he is Begum Hatun's brother.
I didn't know what Karesi Bey
would do so I brought him here.
Let's take him into the dungeon.
Move, move!
-Easy, man.
Yusuf, I was just with your sister.
She'll be very happy to see you.
-If she is harmed even slightly...
-Shut up!
Your sister has a title.
We know that.
But you are nothing.
You did a good job by bringing this traitor.
But this is the first time
I see you. Who are you?
You're right.
I'm new here.
And as to who I am... I'm the alp of
Osman Bey, descendant of Oghuz!
O Allah
You dog
Ilbay!
This dog said he was just with my sister.
The dungeon must be that way.
Let's save Begum Hatun
before everybody wakes up.
Let's go.
Osman Bey Quarters
Attention! Osman Bey!
Alps!
Why does everyone have sullen faces?
Tell me! Why is everyone grieved?
My Bey, they raided our quarters
before we even reached the battlefield.
They killed our Bey, Osman
Bey! That's why we are upset.
You say we should draw back from the war?
Tell me.
You think we should draw back?
Do you want to die in unawareness?
Or do you want to become martyrs
standing upright like the letter "alif"?
We want to become martyrs!
Then get your heads up.
Didn't I tell you
There's no victory without suffering?
This path has thorns.
In this path,
...there is pain
..blood...
...and life.
Didn't I teach you this?
You did
If there is a fire to be started in these lands
...only we can start it.
If there is a fire to be extinguished,
...only we can extinguish it.
-Stop being hopeless already.
-As you order, my Bey!
Saruca.
My Bey.
A Turk...
..can live without a father.
But he can never live without a homeland.
A Bey is required for the homeland.
And the most important
thing for a Bey is weapon.
Bayhan Bey's sword.
It's yours now.
Be worthy of your state,
your morals and nation...
..all the time.
As you command my Bey.
Put grief and sadness aside for now.
No hopelessness!
From now on
..it's time to choke the enemy.
Allah is the greatest!
Yusuf, what are you doing here?
I couldn't have left you to
those dogs. Are you alright?
-I'm fine.
-They're going to take Begum Hatun out! Run!
Yusuf, just leave.
They have Cain's sickness.
They killed Bayhan Bey.
-They'll kill you too.
-I will never leave you, sister. No!
Come here!
Don't shed brother's blood
Even if this leads us to death
...we will get out of here together.
People are coming. Let's go!
How will we get out?
Everybody will wake up shortly.
-Ilbay took care of that.
A cart is waiting in front of the soup
kitchen. They won't even know. Let's go.
Let's put these dogs in the
dungeon first. So nobody will notice.
Come on.
Osman Bey Quarters
When you join the army,
let my alps know this well.
Whoever avoids fighting on the battlefield...
...or hesitates for a moment
won't be forgiven by me.
As you order my Bey.
Brothers, Saruca isn't doing well.
He wants revenge.
That's alright, but...
...he seems to be blinded by his ambition.
...Osman Bey won't mind his suffering...
...but punish him.
You're right, brother.
Attention, Osman Bey!
Begum Hatun.
Osman Bey.
Alps have brought you here alive.
I'm grateful.
Now that you're here to fight...
Saruca, you will hold the right wing.
As you order, my Bey.
Begum Hatun.
You'll lead the left wing.
Your wish is my command my Bey.
But I need to tell you this.
Karesi Bey got Lukas and Sofia's support.
They will be powerful in the field.
I know that.
Boran Bey and Cerkutay Bey...
...are on duty now.
We prepared some plans to
keep them away from the field.
Come on! Everybody to work!
I need to handle something before the battle.
Come on, alps.
You are surprised because I
called you, right, Kanyumaz?
I was able to do so many things thanks to Yakup
Bey, Gonca Hatun. I came here for his sake.
So you care about old days.
Right?
Your humanity hasn't completely
disappeared, has it, Kanyumaz?
If you don't have anything else
to say, Gonca Hatun, I should go.
I do.
I do have something to say, Kanyumaz.
I've known you since I was a child.
When did you become someone who works
with infidel and sheds brother's blood?
Don't, Gonca Hatun.
Shut up!
What's the fault of Karesi Bey's Alps
because he works with the infidels Kanyumaz?
You have children too. Isn't it a sin?
What you've done will only
make Sofia and Lukas happy.
My Alaeddin Bey...
Gonca Hatun.
This is painful for me too.
But that's the order.
Kanyumaz.
Because of Karesi Bey's greed...
...his carelessness, we cannot allow even a
single drop of Turkish blood to be spilled.
If you still carry this in your heart..
..you will do as I say.
Akhisar, the fortress
of the army, which is the...
...leader of discord and which
wants to set Turks against each other.
I have an unfinished plan with you.
Orhan Bey...
Lukas's army is ready to leave Akhisar.
In vain.
They won't even be able to look around.
We will destroy this devilish
army which spreads fitna
and wants brothers to kill
each other with catapults.
-Oghuz.
-My Bey.
Are Boran and Cerkutay Beys ready?
-Yes, my Bey.
They're waiting for your order to fire.
With my order, the attacks
will come from all directions.
Everyone in Akhisar will think they
are surrounded by an entire army.
They will never unite with Karesi Bey.
Turkmens who have been beating
the walls of Bithynia...
and disturbed peace for years will
kill each other on the battlefield today.
Do you know about the great Caesar, Lukas?
The great Roman Emperor
Caesar? How would I not know him?
Every soldier dreams of being like him one day.
Great Caesar was killed by
nobles consumed by power.
And now that same evil ambition is among
the remnants of the Seljuks, the Turks.
And that will never fade until someone dies.
I will unite my army with Karesi's army
and erase Osman from history forever.
The army is ready to set out, Commander Lukas.
Today, our army will defeat Osman.
And my precious Poena...
...will destroy everything Osman has.
Set up the catapults.
The castle of the dastards who have the blood
of Bayhan and our martyrs on their hands.
It will soon turn into the pits of hell.
But for now, the walls will
be destroyed by catapults...
..and the army will be trapped inside.
In the name of Allah, the merficul,
the compassionate.
What is this? What is happening?
Come on Alps!
Let's bring down the enemy's
unclean and unholy walls.
Set it!
Set it, lions!
What's happening
Sir, Turks.
Turks are attacking the walls with catapults.
-Turks How is this possible??
Damn it, when did they surround us?
-Osman...
He must have done this.
Strengthen the gates immediately.
Place soldiers on the walls.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
O The Righteous!
Allah is The Greatest!
O Allah!
O Allah
O The Righteous!
Set it...
We were on our way to the headquarters,
but why did Karesi Bey call us, Beys?
If the messenger wasn't Kanyumaz
Bey's man, I would say it's a trap.
Peace be upon you.
What is Osman Bey doing here?
Osman Bey.
So it was you who called us here.
Welcome, Beys.
Welcome.
They've bought Kanyumaz's
men. They're playing a game.
Turhan, close the door.
Yes my Bey.
Nobody leaves without your permission.
Wait, Beys. Wait. Stand there please.
Now..
...you are Beys..
...who know the Turkish traditions...
...who fight for the world of Islam...
...and who fight in the
battlefield with great bravery.
Karesi Bey, who you follow...
His way is not the right way anymore.
That careless man has
strayed from the path of The Righteous...
...and disobeyed the orders of The Righteous.
He even worked with infidels against
his own people and coreligionists.
Prove it, Osman Bey.
Prove it first.
You are just accusing him.
So you want proof, huh?
Turhan.
Kanyumaz?
Did he betray our Karesi Bey?
He would not.
Allah Allah! What is he doing here?
So that you want to hear the truth...
Kanyumaz. -Beys.
Osman Bey is telling the truth.
Karesi Bey started working with the infidels.
He even tried selling steel
which would kill our men to them.
They both made an agreement
and are slandering our Karesi Bey.
That would never happen
Karesi Bey would never do that!
He did it. He did.
You better not walk on Karesi Bey's path.
If you keep walking on
his path, you should know...
Then your end will be horrible.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you, too.
The attacks continue without
stopping, my Shahzade.
We are attacking Akhisar
from all sides with catapults.
God willing.
We will really besiege the
fortress of this devil soon, my Bey.
We will besiege it. We will.
But let Lukas and his army be
trapped inside that fortress first.
Karesi Bey will be alone in the war.
It will be then Akhisar's turn.
God willing. God willing.
God willing.
-Where are they?
-They are everywhere, sir.
The attacks are hitting
every part of the fortress.
I cannot see
Osman's army around.
It seems they are hiding
behind the trees, waiting to attack.
Now that the devil's dogs
have faced the stones,
they will be scared of
getting out of the fortress.
But we will be careful.
They will not doubt the
siege for a single moment.
And that Karesi Bey...
Karesi Bey will be alone in the war.
Right now! Send the watchmen
Tell them to find the
location of Osman's army! Go!
Osman.
I will fill every hole you made in my walls...
...with your Alps' bones.
Now is the time for war. Come on!
Let's not leave my Bey
alone in his fight with Karesi.
Did Gonca return, Kismet?
No, my Hatun, she hasn't returned.
My Bala Hatun, why did we
come to the graveyard at this hour?
Did you see a dream again?
It's always the same dream, Kismet.
It seems Halime is expecting prayers from me.
Lately...
..I have a tightness in my chest.
You feel that way because Osman
Bey and the Shahzades are at war.
God willing, they will all return safe and sound.
God willing.
Give me the water.
You go to the Sisters, Kismet.
Tell them to be ready.
If they need us, we will go and help them.
My Halime...
In the name of Allah, the merficul,
the compassionate.
I will kill you today, Bala.
So Kanyumaz called you to Osman's
presence on behalf of me, huh?
So Kanyumaz gave false testimony against me.
We never trust their words, my Bey.
Who knows what they gave to
Kanyumaz to make him say that, my Bey?
Oh Kanyumaz.
I will eventually capture and
punish you.
Come, Osman, come.
Come.
Come to your death. Come.
Be proud.
Be proud, Karesi.
Today...
You will become as small
as a grain of this land.
My Halime.
My beautiful daughter.
I am here.
I have you on one side...
..and on the other side...
...my grandchild, who left this false
world without taking a single breath.
The greatest test for mankind
is their children, my daughter.
My beautiful girl.
I am taking your revenge, mother.
Sleep my dear baby
Sleep well in your dream
Quietly and stilly
With angels
Mother?
With birds by your side...
With wind in your hair..
Quietly and stilly
Sleep my dear baby
Commander Lukas.
There is no army outside.
What do you mean there is no army?
Osman
Osman played a game.
He kept us away from Karesi Bey.
Damn you, Osman! Damn you
I thought you would come with all your strength.
But there are many people I cannot see.
Right, Karesi Bey?
Where are the
infidels you allied with?
You could not deceive my men at the inn.
And now you are trying again.
You should know, Osman, you cannot
defeat me with these baseless accusations.
It's time to swing swords like true men now.
Like true men, huh?
Like true men..
My Bey.
Orhan, what is the situation?
I'm coming from Akhisar, the nest of heathens.
Neither Lukas nor the demon
called Sofia nor any of their soldiers...
...will be able to get out of that castle.
Well, Karesi Bey...
Where are your allies?
They're all stuck in the castle.
They can't even take a peek from there.
You're alone, Karesi Bey.
You're alone.
I have no allies expect the
ones standing behind me, Osman.
I have so many powerful Beys...
...and so many loyal soldiers with me.
Who could call such a man alone?
We can beat you, for sure.
With a single word of mine,
...I can leave you all alone here.
Beys
What are you doing
Where are you going?
Stand behind me!
Well... All the beys...
...know what kind of dirty work you are doing.
Kanyumaz, is what Osman Bey says true?
Allah is my witness that it's true.
It's true that he sells steel to heathens
and he's going to fight beside them.
When you see the heathens
on the battlefield...
Karesi will say he didn't call them
but they came by themselves.
Then I won't support Karesi
Bey in this battle, Osman Bey.
You stopped us from making
a huge mistake, Osman Bey.
I'm on your side with all
my strength from now on.
You will keep being on his side.
You will obey him. In fact,
...you'll tell him Kanyumaz is a traitor.
He should come to the
battlefield fully trusting you.
Kanyumaz will take care of the rest.
Everybody in this field
knows about your vile actions.
Karesi Bey.
Stop lying now.
Kanyumaz...
You signed your own death warrant, Kanyumaz.
Kanyumaz!
Come here, Kanyumaz!
Your Bey misses you so much.
He keeps saying your name all around.
Right, Karesi...
...Bey?
From now on my Bey is you, Osman Bey.
May Allah give you a long life to rule us.
Traitor!
Watch your hands and tongue.
Or I will cut them off!
Alps!
Karesi Bey, who we supported and
with whose orders we rushed to deaths
...collaborated with those who want our blood
Now I'm telling you to leave your swords.
Don't lose your lives in vain
Did we risk our lives to
collaborate with heathens?
As Beys don't support you, I won't either.
Your cause isn't my cause anymore.
Shame on you.
Shame on all of you
I didn't know I fed snakes in my arms!
No.
Do you still think you are superior to us?
Tell me.
Will you fight me?
Even if I don't have the
support of Lukas or these traitors,
...while I have your spy Begum Hatun,
...I'm the superior one, Osman.
Alaaddin
Begum Hatun.
You saved her as well, huh?
Whether you fight or not,
...you and people behind you...
..have nowhere to go.
You won, Osman.
You won this battle without
even swinging a sword.
I lost.
You are great...
...and mighty.